Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; Series VII; 15.62; (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings
    - Reel-to-reel tapes
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pêche de nuit" (PT 71), 1957; 1; 00:11:48; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887704)
        Bande unique. ti[?] [?]icicuse; 11'40; mono-38cm.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Ex Plo(x)ions / Les souffles "agrippeurs" de la mer de Barents" (PT 70), 2003; 1; 00:24:42; The end of the program was recorded at a very low level. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887712)
        "Ex plo(x) ions", janvier 2003, 11 minutes; les souffles, avril/septembre 2003, 14 minutes; vitesse 19, sereo.
      - Chopin, Henri. " Bouche souffles et voix" (PT 69), 2005 February; 1; 00:25:30 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887720)
        19 cm/s stereo voix de l'auteur exclusivement montage du meme, studio HC, 24 minutes environ
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le temps aujourd'hui" (PT 68), 1976 December 17; 1; 00:07:28 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887738)
        7'52", 38 cm/s; [milt] + shadow
      - Chopin, Henri. "Staccati en glissandos" (PT 1), 1991; 1; 00:26:13 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507224)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le riches heures de l'alphabet" (PT 2), 1993 January 10; 1; 00:24:53 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507232)
      - Chopin, Henri. " La peur" (PT 3), 1958; 1; This audiotape reel is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507240)
      - Chopin, Henri. " La frise majeure des levres" (PT 4), 2003; 1; 00:35:45 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507257)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le corpsbis" (PT 5), undated; 1; 00:46:15 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507190)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La danse des Tonneaux roulants et brisés" (PT 6), 2003 September; 1; 00:51:52 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507216)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Fresque de l'impalpable voix" (PT 7), 1991 December 22; 1; 00:15:57 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507208)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dynamisme integral" (PT 9), undated; 1; 00:21:06 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507265)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour vivre" (PT 10), 1956; 1; 00:33:07; The program sounds distorted at times. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104506994)
      - Chopin, Henri. "7 audio-poèmes de janvier à octobre 2003" (PT 11), 1; 00:43:15 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507000)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les tubes assassins de Londres..." (PT 12), undated; 1; 01:23:19; All four tracks of the audiotape reel are meant to be played back simultaneously. Fluctuations in the speed can be heard throughout the program. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507018)
      - Chopin, Henri. " Indicatif 1 / La fusée interplanétaire..." (PT 13), 1962-1972; 1; 00:17:10 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507026)
        audiopoèmes, le dernier avec Denis Chopin
        Listed Contents
        "Indicatif 1", 1'
        "La fusée interplanétaire" (annonce de Jean Ratcliffe), 2' 16"
        "L' énergie du sommeil", 5'
        "Le ventre du Bertini", 3' 30"
        "La chanson du parlement eruopéan", 2'
        "Beginning" (poème création de Denis Chopin, effets électroniques H. Chopin), 3' 10"
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le fond de la gorge" (PT 16), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507075)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les Chuintanes respirent" (PT 19), 1979; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507083)
      - Barrière, Françoise. "Le chant des Auriguaciens" (PT 15), 1976 June 23; 1; 00:25:14 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506234)
      - Chopin, Henri. "OU No 30-31" (PT 18), undated; 1; 00:22:08 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506242)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour vivre no 2" (PT 20), undated; 1; 00:36:41 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506259)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dynamisme integral" (PT 21), undated; 1; 00:21:28 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506267)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Staccati en glissandos" (PT 22), undated; 1 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506275)
        Empty, open reel. No files were digitized.
      - Chopin, Henri. "4o Staccati en Glissandos" (PT 23), undated; 1; 00:27:25 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506291)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dynamique integral / French lesson" (PT 24), undated; 1; 00:20:17 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506309)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Plurality 1.1.1.1." (PT 25), undated; 1; 00:09:57 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506283)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Espace et gestes / Pêche d enuit / Sol Air" (PT 30), 1957-1961; 1; 00:47:52 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887746)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Fond de la Gorge / Civilisation de papier" (PT 32), 1974-1975; 1; 00:20:39 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887753)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le palais enchanté des années 80" (PT 36), 1980 March-1982 April; 1; 00:10:28 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887761)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La peur" (PT 38), undated; 1; 00:35:23 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887779)
        ces deux la a producie ensemble en mono
      - Chopin, Henri. "Déplacements hors tout / Les respirations festoyantes" (PT 39), 2003 January-March; 1; 00:26:35 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887787)
        "Deplacements hors tout", 18 minutes 30; "les respirations festoyantes", 8 minutes 07; 19 cm, stereo
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le rire est debout / (Among) II, Johnson" (PT 41), undated; 1; 00:13:09 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887795)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vitesses" (PT 43) (1 of 2), 1990; 1; 00:13:11 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002093778455)
        7 1/2 ou 19 cm; une mono: echos de bouche; deux stereos: double extension & hoppa bock avec Sten Hanson.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vitesses" (PT43) (2 of 2), 1990; 1; 00:09:56 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109978297)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le palais enchanté des années 80" (PT 45), 1980-1982; 1; 00:10:30 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887803)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pêche de nuit" (PT 47), undated; 1; 00:05:53 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887811)
        19 cm/s.; Peche de unit
      - Chopin, Henri. "Cantata for two farts and Juan Carlos the First" (PT 49), undated; 1; 00:12:26; The program is multi-track where all four tracks are played back at the same time. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887829)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le rire est debout / La voix de l'homme dans les éclats solairs" (PT 53), undated; 1; 00:20:40 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887837)
        1) Le Rire est debout, 8'25" 2) La voix de l'homme dans les éclats solairs, 12'54"; mono, 19 cm/s.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Cantate pour 2 pets et Juan Carlos" (PT 54), undated; 1; 00:11:56; The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507281)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le corps" (PT 57), undated; 1; 00:21:13; Audio on the program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507299)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Espace et gestes" (PT 58) (1 of 2), 1959-1960; 1; 00:07:35; The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002093778547)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Espace et gestes" (PT 58) (2 of 2 audiotape reels), 1959-1960; 1 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002093778778)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vertigo du vertige" (PT 59), 1993; 1; 00:11:09 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507307)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le souffle et la langue" (PT 60), 1992-1993; 1; 00:10:42 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507315)
      - Chopin, Henri. "2500 ou les Grenouilles d'Aristophane, et la fortune" (PT 61), 1967; 1; 00:04:32; Static in the audio can be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507323)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La cavalcade échevelée" (PT 65), undated; 1; 00:09:29 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507331)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La digestion / Les éléments" (PT 66), 1972; 1; 00:14:06; Audio on the program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507349)
      - Chopin, Henri. "5 émissions" (PT 67), 1982 March; 1; 01:22:12 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507356)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le temps aujourd'hui" (PT 99), undated; 1; 00:07:30 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507364)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Sol Air" (PT 100), 1961-1964; 1; 00:09:51 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507372)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La digestion" (PT 102), undated; 1; 00:15:40 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507380)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Plurality" (PT 103), undated; 1; 00:19:54 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507398)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Déjeuner sur l'herbe" (PT 104), undated; 1; 00:05:41 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507406)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La peur" (PT 105), 1970 October; 1; 00:55:31 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507414)
        enregistrement du poème
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les vagues et ressacs / La philosophie supreme / Stridences de l'aurore boreale" (PT 106), 2003; 1; 00:23:41 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507422)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pluralité 1111" (PT 107), undated; 1; 00:11:25 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507455)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pluralité 1.1.1.1." (PT 108), 1968-1969; 1; 00:11:39 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507448)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vibrespace" (PT 109), undated; 1; 00:12:16; Static can be heard in the audio. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002104507430)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Fresque de l'impalpable voix" (PT 115), 1990; 1; 00:15:44 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502688)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Fresque de l'impalpable voix" (PT 116), 1990; 1; 00:32:02 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502696)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Alphabet et Glotte" (PT 117), 1989; 1; 00:15:05 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502704)
        7 1/2, 19 cm, stéréo
      - Chopin, Henri. "Indicatif" (PT 118), 1968; 1; 00:16:37 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502712)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Cantata - original" (PT 120), 1975; 1; 00:12:00 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502720)
        Cantata for two farsts and Juan Carlos the first; 11'48", 7 1/2
      - Chopin, Henri. "Audiopoeme no 157 La bouche et le nez (de l'auteur seul)" (PT 124), 2005 February; 1; 00:30:21 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502738)
        Dédié a Francesco Conz
      - Chopin, Henri. "Echos de bouche" (PT 125), 1990; 1; 00:09:55 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502746)
        15 ou 38
      - Chopin, Henri. "Une fête d emicro" (PT 126), 1982 June; 1; 00:07:03 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502753)
        Revox Tape 1, 7'56
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les souffles des Tempêtes" (PT 127), 1993; 1; 00:14:08 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502761)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Three audiopoemes 1973-" (PT 128), 1; 00:12:05 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502779)
        There is a note that accompanies the reel related to its contents.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Hommage to Marcel Janco" (PT 129), 1971 Sept. - Oct.; 1; 00:03:29 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888801)
        Début, amor, ce. 9, 5cm., T.1.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Manifeste poésie sonore" (PT 130), undated; 1; 00:15:38 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888819)
        2) chanson des [pape], 3) vous n'avous pas voix au chapitie
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le voyage Labiovélaire" (PT 131), 1971; 1; 00:08:08 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888827)
        S Press Edition, Germany. oeuvre 2 pistes pour le vieux magnéto, pistes rénies. 9, 5cm
      - Chopin, Henri. 1. Rouge 2. Dyna 3. French Lesson (PT 135), undated; 1; 00:12:56 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888835)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Exodus x 2" (PT 136), undated; 1; 00:17:44; The program is distorted at times. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888843)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Rouge" (PT 137), undated; 1; 00:04:47; The program is distorted at times. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888850)
        audio-poème 1958; Vivre puor Vivre III, 2 pistas
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pluralité Mil" (PT 138), undated; 1; 00:20:18; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888868)
        A la fin retourné bon; laude 19
      - Chopin, Henri. "L'oesophage est un tube escarpé" (PT 141), 2004 April-May; 1; 00:14:17; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888876)
        Composition avec l'oesophage, la bouche et less souffles de l'auteur; durée 14 minutes 20; stéréo, vitesse 19 cm/s
      - Chopin, Henri. "Indie et Sol Air" (PT 142), undated; 1; 00:10:32 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887845)
      - Chopin, Henri. "L'oesophage des crêtes dans les airs" (PT 144), 2003 June; 1; 00:09:29 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887852)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le souffle et la langue" (PT 145), 1992-1993; 1; 00:10:46 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887860)
      - Chopin, Henri. "8 o émission" (PT 146), undated; 1; 00:14:00; The program is distorted at times. (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887878)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le disours des ministres / Symphonie en rut Jambette / A l'impossible nul n'est tenu" (PT 148), 1982; 1; 00:12:35; The program is distorted at times. (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887886)
      - Chopin, Henri. "ABC Radio" (PT 150), 1992; 1; 00:13:48 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887894)
        First broadcast: ABC Radio National, Australia; I/V Henri Chopin with Amanda Stewart; 7 1/2 ips
      - Chopin, Henri. "2500" (PT 151), undated; 1; 00:04:28 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887902)
      - Chopin, Henri. "L'ocean des respirations" (PT 152), 2004 June; 1; 00:05:27 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887928)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le palais virtuose" (PT 153), 1983; 1; 00:14:20; Static can be heard on the audiotape reel. (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887910)
        stereo inedit; voix exclusive de l'auteur, avec variateur de vitesses + effet de larsen. Durée, 4'15". Studio de l'auteur. Trois/mois d'exercice ont été nécessaires.
      - Chopin, Henri. "L'Agrippe des droits piste no 1" (PT 154), 1980; 1; 00:10:03 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887936)
        Au lendemain de l'invasion de l'Afghanistan par 1'URSS. Voix de l'auteur, à propos des Droits de l'homme, bafoués. Plus le poème "Yalta" écrit à Poznan en 1974 où j'ai vu le dictateur général Jaruselski dans sa hauteur de crétin arrive...Ne prendre que la piste 1, durée 8' 41 secondes, vitesse 19.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Throat power" (PT 158), 1974; 1; 00:16:52; There is a gap in the audio from 11:50 to 14:34. (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887944)
        first tape
      - Chopin, Henri. "L'espaces et gestes / Le march commun" (PT 160), 1973; 1; 00:10:30 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887951)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour Vivre II" (PT 161), 1956; 1; 00:09:28; Low level recording on the right channel can be heard from the beginning of the program to 03:25. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502787)
        ministre eu alphabet; 9, 5; 38 cm/s; 2 pistes. Ve[?] radio
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les pets du marché commun" (PT 163), undated; 1; 00:08:05 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887969)
        Discours Ministie; avec une chanson de HC, suivie de caquetiges, de maneailles, de boursouflages buccaux, de rots et de gargarismes, de l'usage de curedents, souligné de légers miasmes stomacaux, le tout inspiré par nos assemblées nationales où nos parlementaires mâchent leurs agressivités â défaut de savoir vivre. Ingatestone, Essex, en 19 cm/s. ' or 7 1/2'. Durée environ 8 minutes 10". Et sans effet secondaire à placer en stéréo. Voix de l'auteur, accompagné de sa bouche. Mono.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les pets du marché commun" (PT 164), 1972; 1; 00:04:35 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887977)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le voyage Labiovélaire" (PT 167), 1971; 1; 00:04:02 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887985)
        piste 1. Pour le Philips. 9, 5.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Thorat-power" (PT 168), 1974; 1; 00:09:05; Program is distorted at times. (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109887993)
        Only my voice is written on the reel.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Hommage to Marcel Janco" (PT 170), 1971 September-October; 1; 00:04:23 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888884)
        Début, second jaune. 9,5cm; T.1, 5'58"
      - Chopin, Henri. "Piste 2 du voyage labiovélaire" (PT 175), 1971 August; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507166)
        1. piste 2 du voyage labiovélaire
        2. la voix de l'homme
        3. copie (mauvaise) de espaces et gestes
        4. bande vierge
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le corps" (PT 176), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507158)
      - Chopin, Henri. " Chat-chat" (PT 178), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507133)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le temps aujourd'hui" (PT 181), undated; 1; 00:15:36; The program is distorted at times. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888892)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les pirouettes vocales pour les pirouettements vocaux" (PT 182), 1995 December; 1; 00:05:34 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502795)
        Voix de l'aueur. Vitesse 38 cm (or 15 inches), stéréo; 5'30
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dialogue desourds" (PT 186), undated; 1; 00:10:52 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888900)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Cantata for two farts and Juan Carlos the first" (PT 187), undated; 1; 00:12:34 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888918)
        Cantata. Cofie. 7 1/2, stereeo; complète avec Jean
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le parlement Européon" (PT 188), undated; 1; 00:07:05 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888926)
      - Chopin, Henri. "La flûte des respirs" (PT 189), 2003 May; 1; 00:12:14 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888934)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Discours ministre" (PT 196), undated; 1; 00:03:38 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888942)
      - Chopin, Henri. "DELFT" (PT 197), 1970 November 6; 1; 00:02:42; The program is distorted at times. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888959)
        Recording with nine students in school en direct et simultane; 19 cm, 2'45"
      - Chopin, Henri. "Discours des ministres" (PT 198), undated; 1; 00:03:36 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888967)
        Portrait - Petales
      - Chopin, Henri. "Soleil mètalique plus clair" (PT 200), undated; 1; 00:09:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888975)
        Original - soleil plus clair; 19 cm.
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le chanson du parlement Européen" (PT 202), 1968; 1; 00:01:54 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888983)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le roc aux peaux grumelées" (PT 204), 2004 April; 1; 00:03:12 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888991)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le ventre Bertini" (PT 205), undated; 1; 00:12:08 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109889007)
        Original. Vietre Bertini 67
      - Chopin, Henri. "Tape 2 Revox" (PT 212), undated; 1; 00:09:11 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109889015)
      - Chopin, Henri / Cobbing, Bob. "Vive Rabelais" (PT 159), 1968 November 3; 1; 00:12:29; Speed fluctuations can be heard throughout the program. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109889023)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Plus j'avance plus je vis" (PT ?) (empty case), 2003 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889734)
      - Chopin, Henri. " Les chaos naturels" (PT ?) (empty case), 2003 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889742)
      - Chopin, Henri. Untitled (PT ?) (empty case), undated (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889759)
      - De Vree, Paul and others. "Holland" (PT 184), undated; 1; 00:31:37 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889031)
        1. Hetleren es en baccaret 2. Kinorama 3. Exodus 4. Oranon 5. Reveil du Chaos 6. Hommage à Orff 7. Papyrofonic
      - Giorno, John / Gysin, Brion. "Subway sound / Bird song / American eagle" (PT 192), undated; 1; 00:10:44; The program sounds distorted at times. (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889049)
        Text by John Giorno; Sound + voice by Brion Gysin; 7 1/2
      - Goethals, Lucien. "Polifonium" (PT 34), undated; 1; 00:11:15 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502803)
        Raffost composition avec audio-poem pour Li magnétos.19 cm; mono
        2.2 De Uitvoering
        2.2.1. Monistisch kunstwerk
        2.2.2. Dualistisch kunstwerk
        2.2.3. Gemengd.
      - Greenham, Lily. "Relativity / Traffic / Tune in to reality" (PT 96), 1973-1975; 1; 00:27:39 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889056)
        Lily Greenham, Lingual music, stereo 7 1/2 for 1) Relativity and 2) Traffic 3) "tune in to reality", tapespeed 3 3/4 (9,5) stereo (1/2 - track)
      - Greenham, Lily. "Seven consonants in space" (PT 172), 1975; 1; 00:03:29 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889064)
        1/2-track, stereo
      - Gysin, Brion. "Pistol poem" (PT 37), undated; 1; 00:17:52; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502811)
      - Gysin / Heidsieck / Chopin. "Petite anthologie" (PT 122), 1960-1962; 1; 00:20:11; The program can be heard only in the left channel from about 13:30 until the end of the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502829)
      - Hanson, Sten / H. Chopin. "Double extension" (PT 46), undated; 1; 00:12:26; The program is multi-tracked. All four tracks are played back simultaneiously. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502837)
      - Hanson, Sten. "Sine tone 5000 HZ for adjusting the level / Sine tone 10000 HZ... / Intermission/ Don't hesitate do it, do it right now / Intermission..." (PT 52), 1969 August; 1; 00:08:08; Digital-sounding static can be heard around 07:40 on the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502845)
        2-track stereo tape, speed 38 cm/s; recorded at EMS, Stockholm
      - Hanson, Sten. "Dance figure (for E.P.)" (PT 169), undated; 1; 00:01:56 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889072)
      - Hanson, Sten. "Revolution / Dance figure / Railroad poem" (PT 180), undated; 1; 00:07:55 (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502852)
      - Heidsieck, Bernard and others. "Heidsieck - Dufrêne - ? - Chopin" (PT 140), undated; 1; 00:15:49 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889080)
        19 cm.
      - Heidsieck, Bernard. "B2B3 - Exorcisme" (PT 207), undated; 1; 00:04:03 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889098)
      - Hodell, Åke. "Numro ba besch" (PT 147), undated; 1; 00:03:16 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889106)
      - Jandl, Ernst. "Vom Lautgedicht" (PT 199), 1974; 1; 00:05:20 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889114)
      - Joyce. "Finnegans Wake extrait" (PT 77), undated; 1; 00:22:25 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889783)
      - Kucharz, Lawrence. "City street scenes I" (PT 149), undated; 1; 00:11:35 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889122)
      - Kucharz, Lawrence. "City street scenes II" (PT 156), undated; 1; 00:11:24 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889130)
      - Küpper, Leo / Frison, Jean-Claude. "Le rêveur au sourire passager" (PT 193), undated; 1; 00:19:24 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889148)
        copie I9 c/s piste pleine, (droits: studio de musique électonique, buxelles)
      - Küpper, Leo. "Innominé" (PT 177), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507141)
        38 c/s, stéréo
      - Leonard, Tom. " Déclamations dérivés" (PT 79), undated; 1; 00:05:21 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889791)
      - Lora-Totino, Arrigo. " 6 phonèmes" (PT 112), undated; 1; 00:27:19 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889809)
      - Lora-Totino, Arrigo. "Phonèmes 7-8" (PT 208), undated; 1; 00:10:22 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889155)
        Vitesse 19., stereo; pour H. Chopin
      - Lora-Totino, Arrigo. "Intonation 5 o ..." (PT 95), 1974; 1; 00:25:31; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889163)
      - Lovano, Maguy / Munro, Vincent. "5 cris gestes" (PT 165), undated; 1; 00:09:07; The program is distorted at times. (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889171)
        Paris, France; 19 cm
      - Lund. "Poi poi" (PT 121), undated; 1; 01:14:36; The program is distorted at times. Speed fluctuations can be heard at 48:30 and for the last minute of the tape. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889817)
      - Lund. "I am..." (PT 123), undated; 1; 00:18:41 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889825)
        There is a list of five tracks described on the cover.
      - Miccini, Eugenio. "Alfabeto" (PT 155), 1978; 1; 00:45:55 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889189)
      - Mon, Franz. "Ja / Nein Parabel" (PT 157), 1971-1978; 1; 00:03:47 (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889197)
      - Novak. "Poèmes onomatopées" (PT 113), 1958; 1; 00:17:11; The program is distorted at times. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889833)
      - Orton, Richard. "Kiss" (PT 211), 1969; 1; 00:06:46 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889205)